天呐 你说话的语气像我妈一样!
Oh, God, you sound just like my mother!
我不知道 我...
Oh, I don't know, I...
我想大概因为
I guess I'd like to think
中学那年 男生女生忙着亲亲的时候
that when the girls and boys were kissing in middle school,
我沉迷于跳舞...
I was a dancer, and...
所以我错失良机
I guess I just missed that boat.
到了高中 他们开始上床的时候
And then by the time they were having sex in high school,
我才试着赶上节奏 献出我的初吻
I was trying to catch up and have that first kiss.
我想我是...
And... I guess I just...
从未赶上他们
never really caught up.
你真的是那么想的吗?
Is that what you really believe?
不
No.
不 我认为
No, I think that there is something
在我的内心深处
really wrong with me,
有些严重的问题...
deep down, that I don't...
我不知道该怎么处理
that I don't work right.
可能你没有生病呢?
What if you're not sick?
也许这种内心深处的感受
What if this deep-down feeling
导致了这一切?
is why all of this is happening to you?
导致了你...渐行渐远?
Why you're just... going away?
也许是的
Maybe.
你相信我吗 凯瑟琳?
Do you trust me, Catherine?
我相信
Yeah.
我想尝试做些事情
I want to try something.
你愿意和我一起吗?
Will you try something with me?
我们一起自慰吧
We're gonna masturbate together.
什么?
What?!
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们一起手淫吧
We're gonna jerk off together.
- 不  - 来吧！
- No. - Yes!
我们可以 我们一起手淫
We are. We're gonna jerk off together.
- 不  - 来吧
- No, we're... - OK, come on,
这对你有好处的
this is gonna be good for you.
不 我不能...
Oh, no, I'm not...
我真的不擅长这个
I've never been good at this.
相信我吧 相信我
Just trust me. Just trust me.
墙里面没有男人...
There's no man in this wall...
我总是手淫
I do this all the time,
- 并且...  - 好吧
- and it... - Great.
总是使我感觉舒服更好
It always makes me feel better.
听着 我会让你擅长做这个的
OK, listen, I'm gonna make you good at this.
高潮很有趣的
Orgasms are fun.
它会释放你大脑中的胺多酚
They release endorphins in your brain,
胺多酚会让你开心 会治愈你
which make you happy, which heal you,
让男人觉得你更有魅力...
which make you more attractive to men...
你明白我说的了吗?
Do you sort of see where I'm going with this?
明白 好吧 我会做的
Yes. OK, I'll do it.
好的 躺好了
OK, get comfortable.
我说话来引导你
I'm gonna talk you through it.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
你躺在一片空地上
You're lying in an empty field.
全身赤裸
You're naked.
你感受到阳光...
You feel the sun...
温暖着你的肌肤...
it's warm on your skin...
它是来治愈你的
and it's there to heal you.
并且有一阵凉爽的微风
And there's a light, cool breeze.
它使你全身发痒...
It tickles you all over your body...
像是一千个的...爱抚你的指尖
like a thousand... mmm... loving fingertips.
感觉好极了
It feels sooooo good.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
现在...
Now...
让微风渗入你的身体
let the breeze penetrate you.
风...完全掌控了你
The wind... it takes over completely now
它让你感到一丝平静
and it fills you with a sense of calm.
它抱着你
It holds you.
这阵风就是你的爱人
The wind is your lover,
它亲吻你 拥抱你
kissing you, embracing you,
抚摸你的每一寸肌肤
touching every part of you.
但是现在
Oh, but now the wind,
它...它被什么东西卡住了
it's... it's getting caught on something.
你胸中的东西正堵着它
Something in your chest is blocking it.
太阳 开始消失了
The sun, it all starts to go away.
风想要通过 你也想要它通过
The wind wants to get through, you want it to get through,
但它就是过不去
but it just won't.
云在天空聚集在一起
The clouds are forming now in the sky.
开始下雨了
It's raining. Yes.
你必须得够到那里去释放它
You've gotta reach down there and free it.
不管它是什么 你必须要捅破
You've gotta clear whatever it is
那层阻碍你的东西  这样才...
that is blocking that wind inside of you, so that...
- 拜托 我在做  - 你没有!
- Please. I am. I am. - You are not!
- 我不行! - 凯瑟琳 你可以的!
- I can't! - Catherine, you can!
我不行! 它总是堵在这!
I can't! It's always been blocked!
不要这么想 你可以! 你绝对可以 凯瑟琳
Stop it. You can! You absolutely can, Catherine.
我相信你可以做到的 你可以!
I believe that you can do this, you can!
我...我可以!
I ca... I can!
- 我...我可以! 我正在做! - 放手去做吧! 捅破它 凯瑟琳!
- I ca... I can! I am! - Fucking do it! Get rid of it, Catherine!
- 用力捅破它 凯瑟琳! - 我...
- Fucking get rid of it, Catherine! - I ca... Ohh! Ohh!
我可以!
I can!
我可以! 我可以!
I can! Ohh! I can!
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
你还有什么需要的话再找我
Let me know if you need anything else.
好的
Yep.
你好?
Hello?
你还在吗?
Are you there?
你当然不在了
Of course you're not there.
因为你是我发疯时
Because you're a figment of my imagination
幻想出来的
when I was going crazy.
这比墙里有个人合理多了
Which makes a lot more sense than a person in the wall,
你个该死的蠢货
you fucking idiot.
我在这 凯瑟琳
I'm here, Catherine.
你怎么样了?
What's new?
我怎么样了?
你现在能看到我吗?
Can you see me right now?
- 我觉得可以 - 那么你应该能猜到了
- I believe so. - So you can probably guess.
我只是想打破沉默
I'm just trying to break the ice.
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
你只是想聊聊天
You're just trying to break the ice.
好吧 你好吗?
Well, how are you?
我患有严重的莱姆病
I have crippling Lyme disease.
我正坐在这该死的轮椅上
I am sitting in a fucking wheelchair
因为我不能走路!
because I can't fucking walk!
- 我很抱歉  - 是吗?
- I'm sorry about that. - Oh, are you?